[{"_id":"634bfe1a97454979393bbe3a","question":"345","language":"PYTHON","code":"323","answers":["v","b","a"],"correct":"2","updated_at":"2022-10-16T12:50:34.854Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634bfece97454979393bbe44","question":"According to my experience, the most frequent usage of it may be requesting for disabling AdBlocks.","language":"JAVASCRIPT","code":"import { IosAirplane } from '@vicons/ionicons4'\nimport { defineComponent } from 'vue'\n\nexport default defineComponent({\n  components: {\n    IosAirplane\n  }\n})","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"1","updated_at":"2022-10-16T12:53:34.390Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634bfedf97454979393bbe46","question":"According to my experience, the most frequent usage of it may be requesting for disabling AdBlocks.","language":"JAVASCRIPT","code":"import { IosAirplane } from '@vicons/ionicons4'\nimport { defineComponent } from 'vue'\n\nexport default defineComponent({\n  components: {\n    IosAirplane\n  }\n})","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"1","updated_at":"2022-10-16T12:53:51.000Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634bfee297454979393bbe48","question":"According to my experience, the most frequent usage of it may be requesting for disabling AdBlocks.","language":"JAVASCRIPT","code":"import { IosAirplane } from '@vicons/ionicons4'\nimport { defineComponent } from 'vue'\n\nexport default defineComponent({\n  components: {\n    IosAirplane\n  }\n})","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"1","updated_at":"2022-10-16T12:53:54.156Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c005e97454979393bbe4f","question":"Qual Ã© a soma?","language":"JAVASCRIPT","code":"import { defineComponent } from 'vue';\nimport { NListItem, NButton, NThing } from 'naive-ui';\n\nexport default defineComponent({\n  components: { NListItem, NButton, NThing },\n  props: ['course'],\n});","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"2","updated_at":"2022-10-16T13:00:14.253Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c68c43ae49021ed610642","question":"Show de question?","language":"JAVA","code":"System.out.println(\"where\");","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"1","updated_at":"2022-10-16T20:25:40.584Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c68c63ae49021ed610645","question":"Show de question?","language":"JAVA","code":"System.out.println(\"where\");","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"1","updated_at":"2022-10-16T20:25:42.539Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c68cc3ae49021ed610648","question":"Show de question? System.out.println(\"where\");","language":"JAVA","code":"System.out.println(\"where\");","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"1","updated_at":"2022-10-16T20:25:48.629Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c87b464cbf6636859e901","question":"Return ?","language":"JAVASCRIPT","code":"\nvar handleClick = function (event) {\n    // do something!\n};\nvar button = document.querySelector('#big-button');\nbutton.addEventListener('click', handleClick);\n","answers":["nothing","null","undefined"],"correct":"nothing","updated_at":"2022-10-16T22:37:40.737Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c8965d07fdd29734865f8","question":"345","language":"PYTHON","code":"323","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"2","difficulty":1,"updated_at":"2022-10-16T22:44:53.723Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634c89ced07fdd2973486604","question":"345","language":"PYTHON","code":"323","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"2","difficulty":4,"updated_at":"2022-10-16T22:46:38.814Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634e94854aeb8e6667bdcf09","question":"345","language":"javascript","code":"323","answers":["1","2","3"],"correct":"2","difficulty":4,"updated_at":"2022-10-18T11:56:53.165Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634e94ac4aeb8e6667bdcf0b","question":"Resultado?","language":"PYTHON","code":"for i in range(1, 11):\n   print(num, 'x', i, '=', num*i)","answers":["1","2","3","ajvascritp","22"],"correct":"ajvascritp","difficulty":2,"updated_at":"2022-10-18T11:57:32.101Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634e95564aeb8e6667bdcf12","question":"Resultado?","language":"PYTHON","code":"# Program to display the Fibonacci sequence up to n-th term\n\nnterms = int(input(\"How many terms? \"))\n\n# first two terms\nn1, n2 = 0, 1\ncount = 0\n\n# check if the number of terms is valid\nif nterms <= 0:\n   print(\"Please enter a positive integer\")\n# if there is only one term, return n1\nelif nterms == 1:\n   print(\"Fibonacci sequence upto\",nterms,\":\")\n   print(n1)\n# generate fibonacci sequence\nelse:\n   print(\"Fibonacci sequence:\")\n   while count < nterms:\n       print(n1)\n       nth = n1 + n2\n       # update values\n       n1 = n2\n       n2 = nth\n       count += 1","answers":["23423","fdsa","sadf"],"correct":"23423","difficulty":10,"updated_at":"2022-10-18T12:00:22.932Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634e96194aeb8e6667bdcf16","question":"????","language":"JAVASCRIPT","code":"# Python program to find H.C.F of two numbers\n\n# define a function\ndef compute_hcf(x, y):\n\n# choose the smaller number\n    if x > y:\n        smaller = y\n    else:\n        smaller = x\n    for i in range(1, smaller+1):\n        if((x % i == 0) and (y % i == 0)):\n            hcf = i \n    return hcf\n\nnum1 = 54 \nnum2 = 24\n\nprint(\"The H.C.F. is\", compute_hcf(num1, num2))","answers":["1","2","3","4","5"],"correct":"5","difficulty":3,"updated_at":"2022-10-18T12:03:37.666Z","__v":0},{"_id":"634e96b84aeb8e6667bdcf29","question":"?2","language":"PYTHON","code":"# Python program to find H.C.F of two numbers\n\n# define a function\ndef compute_hcf(x, y):\n\n# choose the smaller number\n    if x > y:\n        smaller = y\n    else:\n        smaller = x\n    for i in range(1, smaller+1):\n        if((x % i == 0) and (y % i == 0)):\n            hcf = i \n    return hcf\n\nnum1 = 54 \nnum2 = 24\n\nprint(\"The H.C.F. is\", compute_hcf(num1, num2))","answers":["c","b","a"],"correct":"b","difficulty":3,"updated_at":"2022-10-18T12:06:16.787Z","__v":0}]

